Guide to the Insurance Office, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Insurance Office, Yale University, records
1942-1990
RU 521
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
65.5
The records consist of correspondence, policies, statements, accident and injury reports, certificates of insurance, payment statements, and printed materials documenting the activities and operations of the Yale Insurance Office.
Yale University. Office of Finance and Administration
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 5-D (YRG 5-D), Investment and insurance records of Yale University.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details. Files restricted to the office of origin only have been redacted from the finding aid.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, policies, statements, accident and injury reports, certificates of insurance, payment statements, and printed materials documenting the activities and operations of the Yale Insurance Office.
This finding aid contains redacted content. Unredacted version available to office of origin only.
Insurance; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University. Office of Finance and Administration
- Insurance records, 1942-1982; Accession 1983-A-077
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2017
  - Medical School
  - Yale Risk Management
  - Yale Property Engineering, 1975-76 (Box 6, Folder 151)
  - Yale Band, 1974-80 (Box 8, Folder 217)
  - Yale New Haven Medical Center, Inc., 1978 (Box 8, Folder 218)
  - "Wrongful Acts" claim: [name redacted], 1975 (Box 11, Folder 304)
  - "Wrongful Acts" claim: [name redacted], 1975-76 (Box 11, Folder 305)
- Insurance records, 1962-1984; Accession 1985-A-033
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2019
  - Yale Charities Drive (Box 7, Folder 274)
  - Yale Figure Skating Club (Box 7, Folder 275)
  - Yale Law Journal Co., Inc. (Box 7, Folder 276)
- Insurance records, 1960-1986; Accession 1987-A-016
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2021
  - Yale Alumni Publications, Inc. (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Yale Student Tech. (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Yale University Schedule of Insurance (Box 5, Folder 267)
- Insurance records, 1970-1987; Accession 1988-A-027
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2022
- Insurance records, circa 1966-1988; Accession 1989-A-025
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2023
- Insurance records, 1970-1988; Accession 1990-A-030
  - Yale School of Nursing: New Construction Joseph F. Kelly Company, 1976-87 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Yale Auto Body 91929, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 106)
- Insurance records, 1974-1990; Accession 1991-A-017
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2025
  - '85 Chev / Marsh Gardens, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Yale Auto Body, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 137)